Maxim Gryaznov

Portfolio: verymoko.github.io · verymoko@gmail.com · +972 55-271-8504 · Ayanot (central Israel)

Summary

I am an ex-automotive engineer with 2,5 years experience designing race truck parts and units. I also have 3 years experience in the Graphic Design industry as a freelancer. I make not only design, but a technical side also. I want to try myself in the web and app design field.

Experience

Engineer | GAZ Raid Sport at Gorky Automobile Plant, Nizhny Novgorod · 2019—2021

- Configured suspension parts: shocks, bump-stops, sway bars and designed mounts for it.
- Designed suspension parts: leaf spring top and bottom plates.
- Designed a cargo box for rally raid truck.
- Drew up a technical task for a tarp box of the assistance truck.

Graphic Designer | Freelance · 2018 – present

- Designed layout and visual style of web-site for the gift shop. Romanovandety
- Redesigned the mobile app for Android users. · <u>Beer Insiders</u>
- Designed UX flow, layout and visual style for the digital library.
- Designed layout and data visualization of the half year report · <u>Sravni.ru</u>

Frontend developer · 2020—present

- Made an MVP of <u>textelyator</u> (in Russian) a website that helps to create new ideas by denial, insert emojis to imitate SMM texts and insert swear words.
- My portfolio: verymoko.github.io

Education

Nizhny Novgorod state technical university n.a. R.E. Alekseev, Specialist Degree in an automotive engineering

September 2013 – June 2018

Arsenal — National Centre for Contemporary Arts, Graphic and Art Practices course September 2017 – March 2018 · Nizhny Novgorod

Sobaka Pavlova, online UX course

Autumn 2021 · Diploma

Skills & Software

- Soft: CATIA, Figma, Photoshop, Indesign, Blender
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, JS, NodeJS, React, SQL

Languages

- Russian (native)
- English (working proficiency)